Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Books/Magazines/Clippings/Newspapers, 272017
  - Subseries D: Books, 272320
    - Proceedings of The Second International Lewis Carroll Conference, 1994; 274176 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Author: Lovett, Charlie (ed.)
    - The Strand Magazine, Vol.15, January-June 1898; 274177 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - The Strand Magazine, Vol.16, July-December 1898; 274178 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - The Strand Magazine, Vol.21, January-June 1901; 274179 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Surprise Books; Alice in Wonderland, [Undated]; 272368 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Author: Lebeck, Oskar Illustrator: Beckett, Sheilah
    - Tales from Alice in Wonderland, 1996; 274180 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - A Tangled Tale, 1969; 274181 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Visages d'Alice, 1983; 274182 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      Author: Clerc, Cristiane
    - The Walrus and the Carpenter; From Through the Looking Glass by Lewis Carroll, 1965; 272373 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      Illustrator: Rohlicek, Karel
    - Walt Disney; Alice in White Rabbit's House, 1988; 272353 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Cookbook; Favorite Recipes from Mickey and His Friends, 1976; 272350 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Alice Redux -- edited by Richard Peabody, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E: Activity Books, 274155
    - Alice in Wonderland; Color by Number with a Complete Story, [Undated]; 272331 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, [Undated]; 274183 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Alice and Pink Flamingo, [Undated]; 272332 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Alice and the White Rabbit, [Undated]; 272333 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Alice and the White Rabbit, 1975; 272328 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Pictures by Sir John Tenniel, 1972; 272355 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Alice's Wonderland Coloring Book, 1971; 272362 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland; Easy to Read and Color, [Undated]; 272330 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - A Peep-Show Alice, 1989; 272375 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      Two miniature books, The Chess Show and Preface, arranged as a peep-show.
    - Storybook Mazes, 1978; 272323 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      23 mazes based on classic children's stories. Pictorial wraps: 60pp. Page 10 is a Wonderland maze with brief explanatory text and b/w illustrations by the author.
    - Storyland Favorites to Color, 1951; 272341 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Set of four coloring books including: The Blue Bird Coloring Book, Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, The Hiawatha Coloring Book and the Hansel and Gretel Coloring Book.
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Paint Book, 1951; 272360 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - A Wonder Cut and Color Book; Alice in Wonderland, a Doll to Dress, [Undated]; 272344 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Wonderland Storytime Coloring Book, [Undated]; 272359 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Series VIII: Art, 272018
  - Alice and the White Rabbit Tile, undated; 272287 (Box 27, Item 1)
    Square felt backed tile of Alice and the White Rabbit, hand painted
    Dimensions: 4" 7/16
  - Alice (Drink Me), [Undated]; 272288 (Box 27, Item 2)
    Painted, framed glass image of Alice ("Drink Me")
    Dimensions: 5"x7"
  - Leaded Glass Hanging with Chain of Alice and Carrollian Characters, [Undated]; 272289 (Box 27, Item 3)
    Circular colored glass
    Dimensions: 10.5" diameter
  - Alice Among the Flowers, [Undated]; 272290 (Box 27, Item 4)
  - Hand-made Egg Shaped Ornament; Alice and the White Rabbit, [Undated]; 272454 (Box 65)
  - Ostrich Egg Handpainted with Alice Characters, [Undated]; 272455 (Box 65)
  - Alice and the White Rabbit eggshell mosaic, undated; 272645 (Box 73)
    Artwork is a mosaic made out of colored eggshells
    Dimensions: 13" x 12"
- Series IX: Media, 272019
  This series consists of five boxes of sound discs. Disc dimensions are 12, 10, and 7 inch; disc speeds are 33 1/3, 45, and 78 rpm. There is also one box of media; items include video games, audio cd, VHS videocassettes, Viewmaster picture discs, and 8mm motion picture film.
  - Subseries A: Sound and Video Recordings/Computer Games/Films, 272821
    - Alice in Wonderland CBS Irwin Allen Productions, 1985; 272855 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Caedmon Tape, [Undated]; 272860 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Children's Video Playground VHS, 1986; 272850 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland: A Classic Software Fantasy, 1985; 272851 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Interactive Multi-Media CD-ROM, [Undated]; 272859 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland NBC Home Video VHS, 1999; 272857 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Through the Looking-Glass Apple Floppy Disc in Box, 1984; 272858 (Box 67)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, Musical VHS, 1972; 272854 (Box 67)
    - Dreamchild; the Enchanting Story of the Real Alice in Wonderland VHS, 1985; 272856 (Box 67)
    - Four Views of Alice VHS, 1982; 272852 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland, GAF 21 Talking View-Master Reels, undated; 272861 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland GAF 21 View-Master Stereo Pictures, 1952; 278840 (Box 67)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, The Wonderland Quadrilles audio cassettes in box, [Undated]; 272896 (Box 67)
    - Pari Banu Jokes/Songs, [Undated]; 272897 (Box 67)
    - Super 8 Alice in Wonderland, Black and White, Castle films, [Undated]; 272862 (Box 67)
  - Subseries B: Vinyl Sound Discs, 272820
    - 5 Kiddie Favorite Stories by Rocking Horse Records, undated; 272839 (Box 68)
    - Agnes in Wonderland, 1980; 272830 (Box 68)
    - Alice Au Pays Des Merveilles, undated; 272829 (Box 68)
    - Alice In Wonderland, adapted and prduced by Douglas Cleverdon, an Argo Recording, 1958; 272836 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland on Decca Records, undated; 272827 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Original Songs, Junior Records INC, presents Wonderland Records for Children, 1951; 272825 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Musical Drama with Jane Powell, 1947; 272898 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Why the Sea is Salt, Let's Pretend Records, c.1970; 272837 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Why the Sea is Salt, Let's Pretend Records, c.1970; 278819 (Box 68)
    - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs and Alice in Wonderland, vocals by Frank Luther, undated; 272842 (Box 68)
    - Cyril Ritchard Selections from Alice in Wonderland, 1960; 272833 (Box 68)
    - Ginger Rogers as Alice in Alice in Wonderland, 1949; 272899 (Box 68)
    - Chick Corea "The Mad Hatter" Record, 1978; 272828 (Box 68)
    - Original Soundtrack Recording Joel Shaftel's Production of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1972; 272831 (Box 68)
    - Original Soundtrack Recording Joel Shaftel's Production of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1972; 278820 (Box 68)
    - Original Soundtrack Recording Joel Shaftel's Production of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1972; 278821 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland and the Emperor's New Clothes, Rocking Horse Players and Orchestra, undated; 272835 (Box 68)
    - The Simon Sisters Sing for Children Record, 1973; 272832 (Box 68)
    - Argo Presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass 1 of 2, 1960; 272834 (Box 68)
    - Argo Presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass 2 of 2, 1960; 278822 (Box 68)
    - Storyland, Twinkle Records, undated; 272840 (Box 68)
    - Annie in Wonderland, Annie Haslam, 1977; 278823 (Box 68)
    - John Baldry, Everything Stops for Tea, 1972; 278824 (Box 68)
    - Walt Disney's Peter Pan and Alice in Wonderland, 1960; 272841 (Box 68)
    - Songs from Walt Disney's Alice In Wonderland, featuring the Lady in Blue June Winters, undated; 272822 (Box 68)
    - Songs from Walt Disney's Alice In Wonderland, featuring the Lady in Blue June Winters, undated; 278825 (Box 68)
    - Alice au Pays des Merveilles, Livre Disque Philips, 1962; 272866 (Box 69)
    - Alice au pays des Merveilles album disque audio visuel, undated; 278831 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, a Talking Book, complete and unabridged, 1954; 272888 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland Book and Record, Educational, Entertaining Peter Pan Records, undated; 272870 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Meets the Caterpillar and Cheshire Cat and 'Twas Brillig, 1951; 272873 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Meets the Caterpillar and Cheshire Cat and 'Twas Brillig, 1951; 272874 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Meets the Caterpillar and Cheshire Cat and 'Twas Brillig, 1951; 272875 (Box 69)
    - A Musical Story: Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated; 272885 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated; 278832 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated; 278833 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated; 278834 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Musical Story, Peter Pan Records, 1961; 272871 (Box 69)
    - Listen Look picture book, Alice in Wonderland, 1941; 272881 (Box 69)
    - Listen Look picture book, Alice in Wonderland, 1941; 272882 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Story of Alice in Wonderland with Songs from the film, 33-1/3rpm Long Play, 1965; 272867 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Story of Alice in Wonderland with Songs from the film, 33-1/3rpm Long Play, 1965; 272868 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Story of Alice in Wonderland with Songs from the film, 33-1/3rpm Long Play, 1965; 272869 (Box 69)
    - Alicia en el Pais de las Maravaillas, 45rpm, RCA Victor, undated; 272872 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969; 272883 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969; 272884 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969; 278826 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969; 278827 (Box 69)
    - All in a Golden Afternoon from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272887 (Box 69)
    - I'm Late and Alice in the White Rabbit's House, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272880 (Box 69)
    - A Very Merry Unbirthday, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 278828 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice In Wonderland (Title Song) and In a World of My Own, 1951; 278829 (Box 69)
    - Painting the Roses Red, and the March of the Cards, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272876 (Box 69)
    - Painting the Roses Red, and the March of the Cards, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272877 (Box 69)
    - Very Good Advice and Caucus Race from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272886 (Box 69)
    - The Walrus and the Carpenter, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272878 (Box 69)
    - The Walrus and the Carpenter, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951; 272879 (Box 69)
    - White Rabbit by Jefferson Airplane, RCA 45rpm record, 1966; 272865 (Box 69)
    - Lewis Carroll: Alice in Wonderland, a children's music drama, 1947; 272838 (Box 70)
    - Rita Hassan and the American Repertory Theatre Present Eva Le Gallienne's Production of Alice in Wonderland and Through the Looking Glass, undated; 278835 (Box 70)
    - Deems Taylor, Through the Looking Glass, Played by Howard Barlow, c. 1940; 278836 (Box 70)
    - Decca Records Ginger Rogers as Alice in Alice in Wonderland, 1944; 272895 (Box 70)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957; 272889 (Box 71)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957; 272890 (Box 71)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957; 272891 (Box 71)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957; 272892 (Box 71)
    - Alice in Wonderland Story adapted and produced by Douglas Cleverdon, Jane Asher as Alice, box set, 1958; 272900 (Box 72)
    - Alice in Wonderland Story adapted and produced by Douglas Cleverdon, Jane Asher as Alice, Stereophonic box set, undated; 272901 (Box 72)
    - Through the Looking Glass and What Alice Found There, narrated by George Rose, with Sarah-Jane Gwillam as Alice., 1975; 272902 (Box 72)
    - Murray Hill Presents Through the Looking-Glass, Read and Sung by Cyril Ritchard with Facsimile of the book, 1958; 272893 (Box 72)
    - Murray Hill Presents Through the Looking-Glass, Read and Sung by Cyril Ritchard with Facsimile of the book, 1958; 272894 (Box 72)
    - Argo Presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass, box set, 1959; 278838 (Box 72)
    - London presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass, stereophonic box set, undated; 278839 (Box 72)
- Oversize Series II: Housewares/Decorations, 272109
  - Grey on cream wallpaper, Tenniel illustrations, Undated; cuid6202; 272811; 2 items two sheets of wallpaper (Item MSS.368.cuid6202)
    Dimensions: 70"x23.5"
  - Grey on cream wallpaper, Tenniel illustrations, Undated; 2 items two sheets of wallpaper (Roll-storage b)
    Dimensions: 52"x32"
  - Grey on cream wallpaper, Tenniel illustrations, Undated; 2 items two sheets of wallpaper (Roll-storage b)
    Dimensions: 41"x40"
  - Tony Sarg Stenciled Wallpaper, [1930's]; cuid6201; 272784 (Item MSS.368.cuid6201)
    Dimensions: 59"x22"
  - Wall Hanging of the Caterpillar, [Undated]; 272110 (Box 24, Item 1)
    Handmade wall hanging, hand-stitched on burlap, of the Caterpillar.
    Dimensions: 20"x24"
  - Alice in Wonderland Towel Set and Pillow Cases, [Undated]; 272111 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - White Rabbit Felt Yellow Calendar, 1965; 272112 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Alice in Wonderland Orange Felt Banner, [Undated]; 272113 (Box 24, Item 4)
    Dimensions: 28.5"x14.75"
  - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated]; 272581 (Box 44, Item 1)
  - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated]; 272582 (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated]; 272583 (Box 44, Item 3)
  - Happy Un-Birthday Kit, 1962; 272584 (Box 44, Item 4)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream Calendar, Illustrated by Arthur Rackham, 1978; 272585 (Box 44, Item 5)
  - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland by Arthur Rackham, 1979; 272586 (Box 44, Item 6)
  - Alice in Wonderland and its Sequels; a Calendar of Pictures by 12 Artists for 1977, 272587 (Box 44, Item 7)
  - Alice in Wonderland and its Sequels; a Calendar of Pictures by 12 Artists for 1977, 272588 (Box 44, Item 8)
  - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland by Arthur Rackham, 1979; 272589 (Box 44, Item 9)
  - Classic Children's Book Illustrations to Decorate a Child's Room; Alice in Wonderland, [1950's]; 272590 (Box 44, Item 10)
    Title: Classic Book Illustrations to Decorate a Child's Room; Alice in Wonderland
    Description: Set contains 22 Alice in Wonderland wall print cut-outs. Silkscreened.
  - Pink Felt White Rabbit Print on Board, [Undated]; 272941 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    Dimensions: 15"x21"
- Oversize Series III: Games/Dolls/Toys/Puppets, 272284
  - Subseries B: Games/Puzzles, 272301
    - Tea-Time Plastic Dishes, 1945; 272286 (Box 26, Item 2)
      Title: Tea-time Plastic Dishes
      Description: "Hand painted Alice in Wonderland tea time dishes." 22 pieces, original printed box). Alice vignettes cast in relief, floral decorations painted by hand. NB: Alice is not mentioned or illustrated on the box — which suggests that the box is a passe-partout for many different styles of Plasco tea-sets.
    - Alice in Wonderland Game; Follow the White Rabbit Through Wonderland, 1974; 272302 (Box 34, Item data_value_missing_f668fcf01fe3f9faf44f8760404c7bce)
    - Looking Glass Chess set from Alice in Wonderland, 1966; 272303 (Box 30, Item 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Paint Set, 1970; 272304 (Box 74)
      Title: Alice in Wonderland Paint Set
      Description: Alice in Wonderland paint set in a pictorial metal box. Paints and brushes unused.
      Dimensions: 9"x20"
    - Alice in Wonderland Picture Puzzle, [Undated]; 272305 (Box 31, Item 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Picture Puzzle, [Undated]; 272306 (Box 31, Item 3)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 1/8, 1971; 272307 (Box 31, Item 4)
      Title: Cheshire Cat
      Description: An imaginative jigsaw puzzle with big pieces for little fingers.
      Dimensions: 12"x8"
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 2/8, 1971; 272308 (Box 31, Item 5)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 3/8, 1971; 272309 (Box 31, Item 6)
      Title: Tweedledee and Tweedledum
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 4/8, 1971; 272310 (Box 31, Item 7)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 5/8, 1971; 272311 (Box 31, Item 8)
      Title: The Mad Hatter
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 6/8, 1971; 272312 (Box 31, Item 9)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 7/8, 1971; 272313 (Box 31, Item 10)
      Title: Alice Holding a Pig
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 8/8, 1971; 272314 (Box 31, Item 11)
    - Alice and the Mad Hatter Puzzle, [Undated]; 272315 (Box 31, Item 12)
      Title: Alice and the Mad Hatter Puzzle
      Description: Two Puzzles, one side is Alice holding a pig, the other side is the Mad Hatter.
      Dimensions: 12"x18"
    - Alice and the Mad Hatter Puzzle, [Undated]; 272316 (Box 31, Item 13)
      Description: Two Puzzles, one side is Alice holding a pig, the other side is the Mad Hatter. The Mad Hatter is missing six puzzle pieces.
    - Alice Wooden Croquet Set, 1987; 272456 (Box 34, Item 1)
      Title: Alice Wooden Croquet Set
      Description: Set consists of 2 mallets, 2 balls, and six figures painted after Tenniel.
    - Woodette Library - Edition Number 4, [1940's]; 272460 (Box 35, Item 1)
      Title: Woodette Library - Edition No. 4
      Description: Set contains 6 story dolls, one of which is Alice. Designed by Mary Alice Stoddard.
- Oversize Series V: Printed Ephemera, 272637
  - Subseries B: Print Ephemera, 272638
    - Alice's Adventures Under Ground: Excerpts from the Original Lewis Carroll Manuscript in the British Museum, 1965; 272285 (Box 26, Item 1)
      Title: Alice's Adventures Under Ground: Excerpts from the Original Lewis Carroll Manuscript in the British Museum
      Description: Circular jigsaw-puzzle, publisher's circular (cylindrical) box 14¼ inches (diameter) printed in black and white-reserve on salmon-pink ground.
      Dimensions: 20.25" diameter
    - Advertisement from Dairy-Deli Wonderland of Values Sweepstakes, 1973; 272640 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Magazine Advertisements, [1940's]; 272647 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      Title: Alice in Wonderland Magazine Advertisements
      Description: Includes the Original Alice, 7 full-page individual advertisements printed in the Field Magazine over a period of several months in 1949. The artists are identified only as Hanna (5 ads) and Gilroy (2 ads) All of the ads, continue the clever Guinness Alice parodies. And "Oh Mother! Cried Alice. Here's the new Philco fridge" advertisement.
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272908 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      1. Cheshire Cat Print. 2. Alice in Wonderland House Print. 3. Wonderland Print by John Anthony Miller. 4. Lewis Carroll Print. 5. Lewis Carroll Print.
      Dimensions: 1. 10"x13". 2. 5"x6.5". 3. 6"x 6.5". 4. 9"x12". 5. 9"x12".
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272935 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Title: Alice in Wonderland Prints
      Description: 1. Alice Pleasance Liddell. A calligraphic rendering of the Carroll poem the End Looking-Glass. 2. Lewis Carroll's Jabberwocky, a Zalben poster issued by Warne to publicize the book. 3. Scribner's American Painter's Series, No. 3, Down the Rabbit Hole by Saul Schary. 4. The Cheshire Cat.
      Dimensions: 1. 8"x17". 2. 12"x20". 4. 14"x16".
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272940 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      Description: 1. Sepia print of Charles Lewis Dodgson. 2. How Doth the Little Crocodile, by Sarah Chamberlain. Calligraphic reproduction with white ink on black background of Alice's recitation in the pool of tears. 3. Psychedelic Caterpillar smoking his hookah, by Jonathan. 4. Alice au Pays des Merveilles, Disney Studios, RKO Films. 4-color poster advertising the exhibition of the Disney film in France.
      Dimensions: 1. 11"x15". 2. 15"x16" 3. 18"x20" 4. 13"x17"
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272948 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      Description: 1. Alice. 2. Life Magazine Poster board Print of Humpty Dumpty. 3. Yellow Lewis Carroll Exhibition Poster. 4. Fantasy, an Alice in Wonderland Artist's Proof by John A. Miller.
      Dimensions: 1. 20"x15". 2. 19.5"x24.5". 3. 11.5"x10". 4. 18"x23".
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272953 (Folder 3)
      Description: 1. Beyond the Looking Glass of the Patty Hurst Trial by Ralph Steadman, 4 page proof for Rolling Stone Magazine. 2. Alice in Wonderland. 3. Pig n' Pepper by Juan Ripley. 4. Bill Osco's Alice in Wonderland, an X-Rated Musical Comedy. 5. Pool of Tears by Juan Ripley. 6. Croquet Ground by Juan Ripley. 7. Alice and the Caterpillar by Juan Ripley. 8. Pig n' Pepper by Juan Ripley. 9. Alice in Wonderland by Beck Gaurue.
      Dimensions: 1. 23.75"x18". 2. 36.25"x24.75". 3. 34.5"x22". 4. 31"x25". 5. 39"x15". 6. 39"x15". 7. 34.5"x22". 8. 34.5"x22". 9. 28.5"x22.
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272957 (Folder 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated]; 272960 (Folder 2)
      Description: 1. Alice in Wonderland Poster. 2. Alice in Wonderland Poster. 3. Production of Alice in Wonderland at the "Teatr Rozmaitosci W.Warszawie". 4. Cheshire Cat Poster "We Are All Mad." 5. 3 Posters with sketches of Alice in Wonderland Characters. 6. Alice's Tea Party Poster. 7. 4 Posters with Alice in Wonderland Scenes. 8.Cheshire Cat Poster "We Are All Mad".
      Dimensions: 1. 36.25"x24.75". 2. 36.25"x24.75". 3. 37"x25" 4. 34.5"x23" 5. 23"x17.5" 6. 23.5"x17.5". 7. 35"x25.5". 8. 34.5"x23"
    - Alice in Wonderland Restaurant Menu and Place Mat, 1968; 272639 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Companion-Guide to the Exhibition Alice at Longleat, 1973; 272643 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Fashions of the Hour Magazine, 1938; 272641 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Lewis Carroll's Alice's Adventures in Wonderland; the Newberry Library Calendar for 1982, 272321 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Manitoba Theatre Centre Education Kit for Alice Through the Looking Glass, 1971; 272642 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Thirteen Prints Illustrated by John Tenniel from Alice in Wonderland and Alice Through the Looking Glass, [Undated]; 272644 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Posters, 272767
    - 9. Alice in the White Rabbit's Room and 10. Alice Plays at Croquet, Undated; 272790 (Flat-file-folder [small folder])
      Dimensions: 32"x23"
      2 posters - one is damaged
      Artist: Gertrude Demain Hammond
    - Alice and the White Rabbit Psychedelic Poster by Steve Sachs, [1960's]; 272798 (Flat-file-folder [small folder])
      Dimensions: 35"x23"
    - Alice in Wonderland page proof, [Undated]; 272805 (Roll-storage b)
      Dimensions: 38"x27"
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated]; 272913 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      1. Lewis Carroll Exhibit at Pratt Institute Library, celebrating the 100th anniversary of Alice in Wonderland, designed by Willa Percival. 2. Forest Theatre Production of Pygmalion and Galatea and Alice in Wonderland. 3. Alice in Wonderland Presented by the Young People's Theater.
      Dimensions: 1. 13"x 16.5". 2. 11"x 15.5". 3. 17"x 11".
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated]; 272937 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      1. Children's Play of the Season, Forest Theatre Presents Alice in Wonderland. 2. The Bay Theater Collective Presents Alice in Wonderland and Through the Looking Glass.